CV - Monika Louise Bro Høy

+49 15226079017 - monikaalbh@gmail.com - Almstadtstr. 6, 10119 Berlin



As an experienced content manager, I create and edit clear and concise content. I am data-driven and write texts based on SEO. I am experienced in communicating to various user groups and to consider the recipient while telling the good story. Having worked for Microsoft News, I am used to working in a fast-paced environment, with deadlines, and with curating and writing content in areas such as lifestyle, home and interior design.

Work experience

2020 - **Content researcher**

Equalista, Berlin

- Content research and creation
- Writing clear and concise texts

2019 - 2020 Content manager for Microsoft

Wunder Media GmbH, Berlin

- · Content research, creation, writing and optimization for news media
- Translating and proofreading of articles and galleries
- SEO-tasks
- Fulfilling and planning tasks independently

2018 - 2019 Project worker: design of city spaces

Copenhagen Municipality

- · Planning and facilitating projects
- Communicating data and research findings

2017 Consultant internship in a sociological team

NIRAS Allerød

- Comprehensive desk research
- Summarizing research and analysis' to various user groups

Education

2019 - now UX design

Glasgow Caledonian University (online)

• Optimizing user experiences with writing measures

2015 - 2018 MSc in Spatial Designs and Society

Roskilde University

- Qualitative and quantitative research methods
- Written communication

2010 - 2013 Bachelor of arts, European Ethnology

Copenhagen University

- Knowledge and interest in culture and history
- Communication to different user groups

Languages

Danish (native)
English (fluent)
German (B1)
Swedish & Norwegian (basic)

Programs

Microsoft Office CSM's